

# **SKILLS SUMMARY**

- Project Management and Resource Planning
- Customer Success and Revenue Growth
- Leveraging GenAl solutions in Conversational Al
- Conversation Designer
- User Interface Design
- Strategic Automation and Innovation
- User Behaviour Research and Analysis
- Process Improvement

### PROFILE HIGHLIGHTS

- Led execution of India's first connected car with Alexa remote capability
- Conduct Voice and Conversation design workshop in partnership with Google
- Work with market leaders to launch innovative solutions successfully (LLM, Vertex ai, Voice)
- Use cognitive psychology and ethical philosophy to understand and manage AI adoption and design

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Arts Major: Psychology-Philosophy Mumbai University, 2008

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Post Graduate Program in Artificial Intelligence for Leaders
- Prompt Designing for Conversational AI
- Generative AI foundation models and platforms
- Generative AI: Impact and Ethical Issues
- Conversational Design Certificate

## **LANGUAGES**

# SRIMOYEE GHOSHAL

Intelligent Automation I Digital Transformation I Gen AI I Innovation and Strategy I Conversational AI I Project Lead

# +91-9819737044, srimoyeeghoshal@gmail.com

### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

With over 14 years of experience, I am a seasoned professional specializing in digital transformation and innovation strategy. As a strategic leader and program lead in the Conversational AI space, I bring a wealth of expertise to the table. My focus lies in crafting forward-thinking strategies that drive digital transformation initiatives and foster innovation within organizations. I excel in developing tailored solutions that align with business objectives and propel companies into the digital future. Alongside, I am deeply interested in exploring the capabilities of AI and it's profound influence.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Intelligent Automation Consultant (Conversational AI, Gen AI, RPA, OCR, ML)
PwC India I Feb 2022 – present

- **-Lead digital transformation** initiatives, focusing on enhancing user experience and optimizing business processes across Finance, Healthcare, FMCG and Auto industries -Drive **Conversation Design strategies** to constantly refine and improve the user
- journey, ensuring seamless interactions and high satisfaction levels.
- -Analyze existing processes to **identify automation opportunities** and embed Conversational AI solutions for efficient task execution.
- -Focus on refining overall **user interface designs** and elements to elevate user engagement and satisfaction levels.
- -Spearhead the **successful execution of Conversational AI solutions** integrated with multiple automation components, aligning closely with business strategies to maximize process efficiency and effectiveness.
- -Effective client engagement **helping grow businesses** 2x-4x of initial deal size.
- -Continuously monitor and evaluate the performance of automation initiatives, leveraging data-driven insights to drive ongoing **optimization and innovation**.

# **Customer Success Manager (Voice Automation)**

Agrahyah Technologies I Jan 2018 – Jan 2022

- -Developed **design optimization practices** and reusable design patterns in Voice User Interface (VUI) to streamline conversational experiences.
- -Collaborated extensively with **OEM and FMCG sectors to facilitate the adoption of voice platforms.**
- -Develop and implement **process questionnaires to conduct in-depth analysis of user journeys** across different process touchpoints, informing strategic decisions and iterative improvements.
- -Led India's first connected cars launch with Alexa for automobile leaders
- -Held interaction design workshops in association with Google
- -Extensive research and **analysis on user intents** to improve associated customer journeys.

## **VP Client Success (Market-Consumer Research)**

Redquanta | Oct 2011 - Dec 2016

- -Driven client success in the consumer behaviour research space
- **-Designed consumer feedback tools** for both applications and websites to enhance user engagement and satisfaction.
- -Conducted advanced research and analytics to derive actionable insights for businesses, enabling **informed decision-making**.
- -Developed business-effective questionnaires to gather targeted **consumer insights.**

## **Project Coordinator- Level 2**

Packt Publishing I (Mar 2009 - Sep 2011)

- -Spearheaded a high-performing team, resulting in a record-breaking achievement of timely **publishing over 50 books.**
- -Cultivated robust relationships with global authors and reviewers.